Danny Kaye and Sylvia Fine Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Musical Comedy Library (Box 752-864, OV 865, OV 867, OV 869, 870-893)
  - Music
    - Printed Music
      - Choral
        - Springfield, Tom and Jim Dale
          - Georgy girl. New York: Springfield Music, Ltd., 1967. (Box 823)
        - Strickland, Lily
          - Bless his name. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1952. (Box 823)
        - Styne, Jule, Betty Comden and Adolph Green
          - Hallelujah, baby!. New York: Stratford Music Corporation, 1967. (Box 823)
        - Tomkins, Thomas
          - Absalom. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1967. (Box 823)
        - Weill, Kurt and Maxwell Andersen
          - Huckleberry Finn. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1952. (Box 823)
        - Wright, Robert and George Forrest
          - Freddy and his fiddle. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1952. (Box 823)
          - Strange music. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1952. (Box 823)
        - Various Composers
          - Showtime choral collection volume 1 two part chorus. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1952. (Box 823)
          - Showtime choral collection volume 1 three part women's voices. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1952. (Box 823)
          - Showtime choral collection volume 1 four part mixed voices. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1952. (Box 823)
      - Songbooks
        - Berlin, Irving
          - Berlin's best (song folio volume 1). New York: Irving Berlin Music Corporation, 1964. (Box 824)
        - DeSylva, B.G., Lew Brown and Ray Henderson
          - DeSylva, Brown and Henderson song album. New York: DeSylva, Brown and Henderson, Inc., 1927. (Box 824)
        - Lane, Burton
          - The best of Burton Lane. New York: Chappell Music Co. (Box 876)
        - Porter, Cole
          - Songs by...Cole Porter. New York: Harms, Inc. (Box 876)
        - Rome, Harold
          - The Zulu and the Zayda songbook. New York: Florence Music Company, Inc., 1965. (Box 876)
        - Tobias, Charles
          - Through the years. New York: Various Publishers, 1927-50., 2 copies (Box 876)
      - Collections
        - 20 years of hits (from Acuff Rose Publications, Inc.). Nashville, Acuff Rose Publications, Inc. (Box 825)
        - 1000 show tunes (Vol. 2), (Vol.4) (Box 876, 877)
        - 1000 standard tunes (Vol. 1) (Box 876)
        - 1001 show tunes & movie themes. New York: Charles Hansen Distrubor, 1975. (Box 825)
        - Collegiate song book (eastern section). Chicago: M. M. Publishing House, 1929. (Box 825)
        - Collegiate song book (central edition). Chicago: M. M. Publishing House, 1929. (Box 825)
        - Collegiate song book (southern & western Edition). Chicago: M. M. Publishing House, 1929. (Box 825)
        - Songs of Yale. New York: G. Schirmer, 1906. (Box 825)
        - Southern - Peer organization song folio. New York. (Box 877)
  - Scripts
    Scripts from the Musical Comedy Tonight series (I-III), The Danny Kaye Show, and The John Gary Show. Librettos from various musicals.
    Scripts arranged chronologically by show number; librettos arranged alphabetically by title.
    - Musical Comedy Tonight
      - Production materials (Box-folder 827/1-2)
    - Musical Comedy Tonight II
      - Scripts, 2 copies (Box-folder 827/3-4)
    - Musical Comedy Tonight III
      - Director's script (Box-folder 827/5)
      - First draft w/revisions (Box-folder 828/1-3)
      - Master retake script (Box-folder 828/4-5)
      - PA script, 2 copies (Box-folder 828/6-7)
      - Production materials (Box-folder 829/1-3, 830/1-2)
      - Retake script (Box-folder 829/4-5)
    - The Danny Kaye Show
      - #1, LC Record #95-502768 (Box-folder 831/1)
      - #2, LC Record #95-503396 (Box-folder 831/2)
      - #3, LC Record #95-503412 (Box-folder 831/3)
      - #4, LC Record #95-503449 (Box-folder 831/4)
      - #5, LC Record #95-503551 (Box-folder 831/5)
      - #6, LC Record #95-503706, #95-503715 (Box-folder 831/6)
      - #7, LC Record #95-503717 (Box-folder 831/7)
      - #8, LC Record #95-503906 (Box-folder 831/8)
      - #9, LC Record #95-503909 (Box-folder 831/9)
      - #10, LC Record #95-503930 (Box-folder 832/1)
      - #11, LC Record #95-504257 (Box-folder 832/2)
      - #12, LC Record #95-504260 (Box-folder 832/3)
      - #13, LC Record #95-504292 (Box-folder 832/4)
      - #14, LC Record #95-504305 (Box-folder 832/5)
      - #15, LC Record #95-504328 (Box-folder 832/6)
      - #16, LC Record #95-504337 (Box-folder 832/7)
      - #17, LC Record #95-504339 (Box-folder 832/8)
      - #18, LC Record #95-504343 (Box-folder 832/9)
      - #19, LC Record #95-504361, #95-504365 (Box-folder 832/10)
      - #20, LC Record #95-504373 (Box-folder 833/1)
      - #21, LC Record #95-504377 (Box-folder 833/2)
      - #22, LC Record #95-504540 (Box-folder 833/3)
      - #23, LC Record #95-504782 (Box-folder 833/4)
      - #24, LC Record #95-504862 (Box-folder 833/5)
      - #25, LC Record #95-505229 (Box-folder 833/6)
      - #26, LC Record #95-505041 (Box-folder 833/7)
      - #27, LC Record #95-505143 (Box-folder 833/8)
      - #28, LC Record #95-505230 (Box-folder 833/9)
      - #29, LC Record #95-505406, #95-505454 (Box-folder 833/10)
      - #30, LC Record #95-505559 (Box-folder 833/11)
      - #31, LC Record #95-505681 (Box-folder 834/1)
      - #32, LC Record #95-505758, #95-506185 (Box-folder 834/2)
      - #33, LC Record #95-506002 (Box-folder 834/3)
      - #34, LC Record #95-506008 (Box-folder 834/4)
      - #35, LC Record #95-506488 (Box-folder 834/5)
      - #36, LC Record #95-506557 (Box-folder 834/6)
      - #37, LC Record #95-506611, #95-507058, #95-507063 (Box-folder 834/7)
      - #38, LC Record #95-507692 (Box-folder 834/8)
      - #39, LC Record #95-507895 (Box-folder 834/9)
      - #40, LC Record #95-508025 (Box-folder 834/10)
      - #41, LC Record #95-508243 (Box-folder 834/11)
      - #42, LC Record #95-508332, #95-508359 (Box-folder 835/1)
      - #43, LC Record #95-508405 (Box-folder 835/2)
      - #44, LC Record #95-508565 (Box-folder 835/3)
      - #45, LC Record #95-508803 (Box-folder 835/4)
      - #46, LC Record #95-508805 (Box-folder 835/5)
      - #47, LC Record #95-508806 (Box-folder 835/6)
      - #48, LC Record #95-508981 (Box-folder 835/7)
      - #49, LC Record #95-508998 (Box-folder 835/8)
      - #50, LC Record #95-509142 (Box-folder 835/9)
      - #51, LC Record #95-509142 (Box-folder 835/10)
      - #52, LC Record #95-509303 (Box-folder 836/1)
      - #53, LC Record #95-509315 (Box-folder 836/2)
      - #54, LC Record #95-509334 (Box-folder 836/3)
      - #55, LC Record #95-509409 (Box-folder 836/4)
      - #56, LC Record #95-509458 (Box-folder 836/5)
      - #57, LC Record #95-509662 (Box-folder 836/6)
      - #58, LC Record #95-509663 (Box-folder 836/7)
      - #59, LC Record #95-509705 (Box-folder 836/8)
      - #60, LC Record #95-509707 (Box-folder 836/9)
      - #61, LC Record #95-509781 (Box-folder 836/10)
      - #62, LC Record #95-509983 (Box-folder 836/11)
      - #63, LC Record #95-510104 (Box-folder 837/1)
      - #64, LC Record #95-510202 (Box-folder 837/2)
      - #65, LC Record #95-510272 (Box-folder 837/3)
      - #66, LC Record #95-510594 (Box-folder 837/4)
      - #67, LC Record #95-510595, #95-510596 (Box-folder 837/5)
      - #68, LC Record #95-510597 (Box-folder 837/6)
      - #69, LC Record #95-510715, #95-510721 (Box-folder 837/7)
      - #70, LC Record #95-510737, #95-510738 (Box-folder 837/8)
      - #71, LC Record #95-510920 (Box-folder 837/9)
      - #72, LC Record #95-510996 (Box-folder 837/10)
      - #73, LC Record #95-510999 (Box-folder 837/11)
      - #74, LC Record #95-511332 (Box-folder 838/1)
      - #75, LC Record #95-511333 (Box-folder 838/2)
      - #76, LC Record #95-511334 (Box-folder 838/3)
      - #77, LC Record #95-511363 (Box-folder 838/4)
      - #78, LC Record #95-511335 (Box-folder 838/5)
      - #79, LC Record #95-511364 (Box-folder 838/6)
      - #80, LC Record #95-511367 (Box-folder 838/7)
      - #81, LC Record #95-511530 (Box-folder 838/8)
      - #82, LC Record #95-511574 (Box-folder 838/9)
      - #83, LC Record #95-511588 (Box-folder 838/10)
      - #84, LC Record #95-511640 (Box-folder 838/11)
      - #85, LC Record #95-511809 (Box-folder 839/1)
      - #86, LC Record #95-512164, #95-512165 (Box-folder 839/2)
      - #87, LC Record #95-512166 (Box-folder 839/3)
      - #88, LC Record #95-512214, #95-512219 (Box-folder 839/4)
      - #89, LC Record #95-512225 (Box-folder 839/5)
      - #90, LC Record #95-512296 (Box-folder 839/6)
      - #91, LC Record #95-512657 (Box-folder 839/7)
      - #92, LC Record #95-512658 (Box-folder 839/8)
      - #93, LC Record #95-512659 (Box-folder 839/9)
      - #94, LC Record #95-512660 (Box-folder 839/10)
      - #95, LC Record #95-517712 (Box-folder 839/11)
      - #96, LC Record #95-518058 (Box-folder 840/1)
      - #97, LC Record #95-518102 (Box-folder 840/2)
      - #98, LC Record #95-518115 (Box-folder 840/3)
      - #99, LC Record #95-518235 (Box-folder 840/4)
      - #100, LC Record #95-518266 (Box-folder 840/5)
      - #101, LC Record #95-518307 (Box-folder 840/6)
      - #102, LC Record #95-518444 (Box-folder 840/7)
      - #103, LC Record #95-518495 (Box-folder 840/8)
      - #104, LC Record #95-518503 (Box-folder 840/9)
      - #105, LC Record #95-518574 (Box-folder 840/10)
      - #106, LC Record #95-518650 (Box-folder 840/11)
      - #107, LC Record #95-518809 (Box-folder 841/1)
      - #108, LC Record #95-518916 (Box-folder 841/2)
      - #109, LC Record #95-518972 (Box-folder 841/3)
      - #110, LC Record #95-518983 (Box-folder 841/4)
      - #111, LC Record #95-519058 (Box-folder 841/5)
      - #112, LC Record #95-519065 (Box-folder 841/6)
      - #113, LC Record #95-519401 (Box-folder 841/7)
      - #114, LC Record #95-519490 (Box-folder 841/8)
      - #115, LC Record #95-519496 (Box-folder 841/9)
      - #116, LC Record #95-519560 (Box-folder 841/10)
      - #117, LC Record #95-519568 (Box-folder 841/11)
      - #118, LC Record #95-519821 (Box-folder 841/12)
      - #119, LC Record #95-519945 (Box-folder 842/1)
      - #120, LC Record #95-520054 (Box-folder 842/2)
      - #121, LC Record #95-520063 (Box-folder 842/3)
      - #122, LC Record #95-520157 (Box-folder 842/4)
      - #123, LC Record #95-520282 (Box-folder 842/5)
      - #124, LC Record #95-520319 (Box-folder 842/6)
    - The John Gary Show
      - #1 - #12, There is a card from a fan between pp.33 & 34 of script #6 (Box-folder 843/1-8, 844/1-4)
    - Librettos
      - The act. George Furth (Box-folder 845/1)
      - All American. Mel Brooks (Box-folder 845/2)
      - All in love. Bruce Geller (Box-folder 845/3)
      - Allegro. Oscar Hammerstein II, 2 copies (Box-folder 845/4)
      - Annie get your gun. Herbert and Dorothy Fields, 2 copies (Box-folder 845/5)
      - Anyone can whistle. Arthur Laurents (Box-folder 845/6)
      - Anything goes. Guy Bolton and P.G. Wodehouse, 2 copies (Box-folder 845/7-8)
      - Applause. Betty Comden and Adolph Green (Box-folder 846/1)
      - The apple tree. Jerome Coopersmith (Box-folder 846/2)
      - As thousands cheer. Moss Hart and Irving Berlin, 2 copies (Box-folder 846/3-4)
      - At home abroad. Howard Dietz, 2 copies (Box-folder 846/5)
      - Babes in arms. Goerge Oppenheimer, 2 copies (Box-folder 846/6-7)
      - The band wagon. George S. Kaufman and Howard Dietz, 2 copies (Box-folder 847/1-2)
      - The body beautiful. Joseph Stein and Will Glickman (Box-folder 847/3)
      - The boyfriend. Sandy Wilson (Box-folder 847/4)
      - The boys from Syracuse. George Abbott, 2 copies (Box-folder 847/5)
      - By Jupiter. Richard Rodgers and Lorenz Hart, 2 copies (Box-folder 847/6-7)
      - Bye bye birdie. Michael Stewart (Box-folder 847/8)
      - Cabaret. Joe Masteroff, 2 copies (Box-folder 848/1)
      - Call me madam. Howard Lindsay and Russell Crouse (Box-folder 848/2)
      - Camelot. Alan Jay Lerner, 2 copies (Box-folder 848/3)
      - Can-can. Abe Burrows (Box-folder 848/4)
      - Candide. Hugh Wheeler (Box-folder 848/5)
      - Canterbury tales. Martin Starkie and Nevill Coghill (Box-folder 848/6)
      - Carousel. Benjamin Glazer, 2 copies (Box-folder 848/7)
      - Celebration. Tom Jones and Harry Schmidt (Box-folder 848/8)
      - Company. George Furth, 2 copies (Box-folder 849/1)
      - A Connecticut yankee. Herbert Fields, 2 copies (Box-folder 849/2)
      - Curley McDimple. Robert Dahdah and Mary Boylan (Box-folder 849/3)
      - Dames at sea. George Haimsohn and Rob Miller, 2 copies (Box-folder 849/4)
      - Damn Yankees. George Abbott and Douglas Wallop (Box-folder 849/5)
      - The desert song. Otto Harbach, Frank Mandel and Oscar Hammerstein (Box-folder 849/6)
      - The education of Hyman Kaplan. Benjamin Bernard Zavin (Box-folder 849/7)
      - Fade out - fade in. Betty Comden and Adolph Green, 2 copies (Box-folder 849/8)
      - The fantasticks. Tom Jones, 2 copies (Box-folder 849/9)
      - Fiddler on the roof. Joseph Stein, 2 copies (Box-folder 850/1)
      - Finian's rainbow. E.Y. Harburg and Fred Saidy (Box-folder 850/2)
      - Fiorello. Jerome Weidman and George Abbott (Box-folder 850/3)
      - First impressions. Abe Burrows (Box-folder 850/4)
      - Flora the red menace. George Abbott and Robert Russell (Box-folder 850/5)
      - Follies. James Goldman, 2 copies (Box-folder 850/6)
      - Frank Merriwell. Skip Redwine, Larry Frank and Heywood Gould (Box-folder 850/7)
      - A funny thing happened on the way to the forum. Burt Shevelove and Larry Gelbart (Box-folder 850/8)
      - Gentlemen prefer blondes. Joseph Fields and Anita Loos (Box-folder 850/9)
      - George Washington, Jr. George M. Cohan (Box-folder 851/1)
      - Girl crazy. Guy Bolton and Jack McGowen, 2 copies (Box-folder 851/2-3)
      - Golden boy. Clifford Odets and William Gibson, 2 copies (Box-folder 851/4)
      - Goldilocks. Joan Ford, Walter and Jean Kerr (Box-folder 851/5)
      - Good news. Lawrence Scwab and B.G. DeSylva, 2 copies (Box-folder 851/6)
      - The grass harp. Kenward Elmslie (Box-folder 851/7)
      - Grease. Jim Jacobs and Warren Casey (Box-folder 851/8)
      - Greenwillow. Lesser Samuels (Box-folder 851/9)
      - Guys and dolls. Jo Swerling and Abe Burrows, 2 copies (Box-folder 851/10)
      - H.M.S. pinnafore. W.S. Gilbert (Box-folder 852/1)
      - Half a sixpence. Beverly Cross (Box-folder 852/2)
      - Happy hunting. Howard Lindsey and Russel Crouse (Box-folder 852/3)
      - The happy time. N. Richard Nash (Box-folder 852/4)
      - Henry sweet Henry. Nunally Johnson (Box-folder 852/5)
      - The Hollywood pinafore. George S. Kaufman (Box-folder 852/6)
      - How now, dow Jones. Max Schulman (Box-folder 852/7)
      - How to succeed in business without really trying. Abe Burrows, Jack Weinstock and Willie Gilbert, 2 copies (Box-folder 852/8)
      - I do, I do. Tom Jones (Box-folder 852/9)
      - I love my wife. Michael Stewart (Box-folder 852/10)
      - I'd rather be right. George S. Kaufman and Moss Hart, 2 copies (Box-folder 852/11)
      - Inspector general. Nikolai Gogol (Box-folder 853/1)
      - It's Superman!. David Newman and Robert Benton (Box-folder 853/2)
      - Jacques Brel is alive and well and living in Paris. Eric Blau and Mort Shuman (Box-folder 853/3)
      - Johnny Johnson. Paul Green (Box-folder 853/4)
      - Jubilee. Moss Hart (Box-folder 853/5)
      - The king and I. Oscar Hammerstein II, 2 copies (Box-folder 853/6)
      - Kismet. Charles Lederer and Luther Davis (Box-folder 853/7)
      - Kiss me Kate. Samuel and Bella Spewack, 2 copies (Box-folder 853/8)
      - Kuprin. Jerome Lawrence and Robert E. Lee (Box-folder 853/9)
      - Lady Audley's secret. Douglas Seale (Box-folder 853/10)
      - Lady be good. Guy Bolton and Fred Thomason (Box-folder 854/1)
      - Lady in the dark. Moss Hart, 2 copies (Box-folder 854/2)
      - Leave it to Jane. Guy Bolton and P.G. Wodehouse, 2 copies (Box-folder 854/3-4)
      - Lend an ear. Charles Gaynor (Box-folder 854/5)
      - Let 'em eat cake. George S. Kaufman and Morrie Ryskind, 2 copies (Box-folder 854/6-7)
      - Little Johnny Jones. George M. Cohan (Box-folder 854/8)
      - Little me. Neil Simon (Box-folder 855/1-2)
      - A little night music. Hugh Wheeler (Box-folder 855/3)
      - The little prince. Alan Jay Lerner, 2 copies (Box-folder 855/4)
      - Little women. John Ravold (Box-folder 855/5)
      - Lock up your daughters. Bernard Niles (Box-folder 855/6)
      - Lovely ladies, kind gentlemen. John Patrick (Box-folder 855/7)
      - Lute song. Will Irwin and Sidney Howard (Box-folder 855/8)
      - Mack & Mabel. Michael Stewart (Box-folder 856/1)
      - Maggie Flynn. Hugo Peretti and Morton DaCosta (Box-folder 856/2)
      - Mame. Jerome Lawrence, 2 copies (Box-folder 856/3)
      - Man of la Mancha. Dale Wasserman, 2 copies (Box-folder 856/4)
      - Me and Juliet. Oscar Hammerstein II, 2 copies (Box-folder 856/5)
      - The most happy fella. Frank Loesser, 2 copies (Box-folder 856/6)
      - Mr. President. Howard Lindsay and Russel Crous (Box-folder 856/7)
      - Music man. Meredith Wilson (Box-folder 856/8)
      - My fair lady. Alan Jay Lerner, 2 copies (Box-folder 856/9-10)
      - New girl in town. George Abbott (Box-folder 857/1)
      - No strings. Samuel Taylor, 2 copies (Box-folder 857/2)
      - Now is the time for all good men. Gretchen Cryer (Box-folder 857/3)
      - O marry me!. Lola Pergament (Box-folder 857/4)
      - Of thee I sing. George S. Kaufman and Morrie Ryskind, 2 copies (Box-folder 857/5)
      - Oh boy! Guy Bolton (Box-folder 857/6)
      - Oh, Kay! Guy Bolton and P.G. Wodehouse (Box-folder 857/7)
      - Oklahoma! Oscar Hammerstein, 2 copies (Box-folder 857/8)
      - On a clear day you can see forever. Alan Jay Lerner (Box-folder 858/1)
      - Once upon a mattress. Jay Thompson, Marshall Barer and Dean Fuller (Box-folder 858/2)
      - One touch of Venus. S.J. Perelman and Ogden Nash (Box-folder 858/3)
      - The pajama game. George Abbott and Richard Bissell, 2 copies (Box-folder 858/4)
      - Pal Joey. John O'Hara, 2 copies (Box-folder 858/5)
      - Panama Hattie. Herbert Fields and B.G. DeSylva, 2 copies (Box-folder 858/6)
      - Phileron. Tom Jones (Box-folder 858/7)
      - Pippin. Roger O. Hirson (Box-folder 858/8)
      - Pirates of Penzance. W.S. Gilbert (Box-folder 859/1)
      - Plain and fancy. Joseph Stein and Will Glickman, 2 copies (Box-folder 859/2)
      - Poor Bitos. Jean Anouilh (Box-folder 859/3)
      - Purlie. Davis-Rose-Udell (Box-folder 859/4)
      - Red head. Herbert and Dorothy Fields, David Shaw (Box-folder 859/5)
      - Salvation. C.C. Courtney and Peter Link (Box-folder 859/6)
      - The secret life of Walter Mitty. Joe Manchester (Box-folder 859/7)
      - Seesaw. Michael Bennett (Box-folder 859/8)
      - Seventeen. Sally Benson, 2 copies (Box-folder 859/9)
      - 1776. Peter Stone (Box-folder 859/10)
      - Shenandoah. James Lee Barrett (Box-folder 859/11)
      - Show boat. Oscar Hammerstein II, 2 copies (Box-folder 859/12)
      - Show me where the good times are. Lee Thuna, 2 copies (Box-folder 860/1)
      - Silk stockings. George S. Kaufman, Leueen MacGrath and Abe Burrows (Box-folder 860/2)
      - Skyscraper. Peter Stone, 2 copies (Box-folder 860/3)
      - The sound of music. Howard Lindsay and Russel Crouse, 2 copies (Box-folder 860/4)
      - South Pacific. Oscar Hammerstein II and Joshua Logan, 2 copies (Box-folder 860/5-6)
      - Street scene. Elmer Rice, 2 copies (Box-folder 861/1-4)
      - Strike up the band. George S. Kaufman, 2 copies (Box-folder 861/5-6)
      - Sweet charity. Neil Simon, 2 copies (Box-folder 861/7)
      - Take her she's mine. Phoebe and Henry Ephron (Box-folder 862/1)
      - The thirteen clocks. James Thurber (Box-folder 862/2)
      - Tom Sawyer. Frank Luther (Box-folder 862/3)
      - Trial by jury. W .S. Gilbert, 2 copies (Box-folder 862/4)
      - Twentieth century. Betty Comden and Adolph Green (Box-folder 862/5)
      - Two by two. Peter Stone (Box-folder 862/6)
      - Two gentlemen of Verona. John Guare and Mel Shapiro (Box-folder 862/7)
      - The unsinkable Molly Brown. Richard Morris (Box-folder 862/8)
      - Walking happy. Roger O. Hirson and Ketti Fring (Box-folder 863/1)
      - West side story. Arthur Laurents, 2 copies (Box-folder 863/2)
      - What makes Sonny run? Bud Schulberg and Stuart Schulberg (Box-folder 863/3)
      - Where's Charley? George Abbott, 2 copies (Box-folder 863/4)
      - Wish you were here. Arthur Kober and Joshua Logan (Box-folder 863/5)
      - Wonderful town. Joseph Fields and Jerome Chodorov (Box-folder 863/6)
      - You touched me. Tennessee Williams and Donald Windham (Box-folder 863/7)
      - You're a good man Charlie Brown. Clark Gesner, 2 copies (Box-folder 863/8)
      - Your own thing. Donald Driver, 2 copies (Box-folder 864/1)
      - Zorba. Joseph Stein (Box-folder 864/2)
  - Books
    Arranged alphabetically by author, and alphabetically by title therein.
    - Alexander, Ronald. Time out for Ginger
    - Bach, Bob and Ginger Mercer. Our Huckleberry friend (The life and times of Johnny Mercer)
    - Barlow, Harold and Sam Morgenstern. (A dictionary of) musical themes
    - Barrie, J.M. The admirable Crichton
    - Brown, Porter Emerson. The bad man, 2 copies
    - Buchanan, Thompson. Civilian clothes
    - Carpenter, Edward Childs. Connie goes home
    - The Chappel Group. Comprehensive catalogue of vocal solos, Marked as "the property of The Danny Kaye Show" on inside front cover, 2 copies
    - Charles Hansen Educational Sheet Music and Books
      - (A selective musical collection of the) world's greatest hits of the twenties
      - (A selective musical collection of the) world's greatest hits of the thirties
    - Chekhov, Anton. The brute and other farces
    - Deval, Jacques. Tovarich
    - Dietrichstein, Leo. Are you a mason?, 2 copies
    - Ford, Ford Madox. The good soldier
    - French, Samuel. (Basic) catalogue of plays
    - Gow, Ronald and Walter Greenwood. Love on the dole
    - Hackett, Walter. Captain Applejack
    - Harrison, G .B. (editor). A midsummer night's dream
    - Holm, John Cecil and George Abbott. Three men on a horse, 2 copies
    - Kaufman, George S. and Edna Ferber. The royal family
    - Knoblock, Edward. My lady's dress
    - Maugham, W.S. The letter
    - Molnar, Ferenc. The swan
    - Murray, John and Allen Boretz. Room service
    - Nicholson, Kenyon. The barker
    - O'Casey, Sean. Juno and the paycock
    - Phillips, John S. The payers (occasional pieces)
    - Pinero, Arthur W. The gay Lord Quex
    - Royle, Edwin Milton. Launcelot and Elaine
    - Scott, Allan and George Haight. Goodbye again
    - Simpson, Harold and Morris Harvey. The "nine o'clock revue" book
    - Smith, Harry James. A tailor-made man
    - Smith, Winchell. The fortune hunter
    - Stecheson, Anthony and Anne (compilers). (The Stecheson) classified song directory, Marked "The Danny Kaye show" on inside front cover
    - Stevens, Leslie. The marriage-go-round
    - Strong, Austin. Seventh heaven
    - United Artists Music
      - Popular songs (volumes 1-5)
      - Super standards (volumes 1-5)
    - van Druten, John. Behold, we live
    - Warner, Alan. Who sang what (on the screen), Autographed by "Gus IV" for Sylvia Fine on title page
    - Warner Bros. Publications Inc.100 best songs (of the 20's and 30's), Autographed by "Gus IV" for Sylvia Fine on title page
    - Watson, Thomas A. The birth and babyhood of the telephone
    - Watters, George Manker and Arthur Hopkins. Burlesque
    - Wedge, George A. Keyboard harmony, Markings by Sylvia Fine on inside front and back covers
    - Wooll, Edward. Libel!, 2 copies
  - Slides
    2" negatives of the Musical Comedy Tonight series, Broadway musical productions, composers, and writers.
    Arranged alphabetically by title or personal name.